Hello friends, I am Nitin Mittal. Today
I have brought for you ICC Prudential
Company's new product Protest and Ball.
If you are looking for a term insurance
which gives you family security as well as
higher returns, then this is the same plan. Yes,
term insurance and that too with higher returns. To
understand the plan better,
watch the video further. So let's start.
In this policy, you get insurance 100 times the premium.
In this, you get insurance in case of death due to accident
or in case of becoming incapable of reducing due to accident.
Along with this, you get insurance in case of death due to illness.
In this policy, you also get tax benefit in ATC.
In all term insurances, you have to
provide income proof,
but in this policy, you have to declare your income till the age of 45. You do
not have to file any ITR.
Similarly, your minimum income should be 300
years. In this policy, there is a
video medical of those below 45 years of age.
They do not have to go to their house or
anyone comes to their house for medical examination. Now, let's take an
example.  Let us assume that a woman is 35 years old
and wants to take insurance till the age of 75 years
and she wants to pay the premium only
for 10 years and if she
survives till the age of 75 then she will
get Rs 42 lakh indirectly. That woman had paid
approximately Rs 6.5 lakh in 10 years at the rate of Rs 64872 per year
because in this plan your
premium amount is invested in mutual funds
hence you also
get high returns. Now let us take another example,
a woman is 35 years old and
wants to take insurance till the age of 75 years. That woman pays a
premium of Rs 55300 per year for a period of 40 years,
so she paid a total premium of Rs 22 lakh
12000 to the company. Now
after a period of 40 years she will get approximately Rs 1 crore 25 lakh. Yes
you heard it right,
Rs 1 crore 25 lakh and we assume
that if her death occurs
in the middle of the policy due to an accident then the nominee will get Rs 50
lakh +  An additional ₹50 lakh will be given in case of death due to an accident,
so the nominee will receive a total of ₹1
crore, and in case of death due to illness, the
nominee will receive ₹50 lakh.
Also note that if the fund value is
more than ₹50 lakh, the nominee will
receive only the fund value, and if the fund
value is less than the sum insured, the nominee will
receive the sum insured of ₹50 lakh.
This is the return history of the mutual fund. From this, you
can understand how powerful investing in mutual funds is.
Pause the video and see the 10-year returns in the table.
Almost every mutual fund has
given a return of 15% plus in 10 years. The special feature of this plan is
that from the 11th year, the company doubles the
mortality charge and allocation charge deducted in the policy and
returns it to you.
Also, in the last 5 years of the policy, the
company gives you an extra 20% booster on the fund value of the last 5 years.
This feature is an industry first
and for the first time in this company.  This
policy allows you to invest in funds of your choice,
and you
can also change the fund after purchasing the policy. You can choose
from five portfolio strategies.
For more information, read the policy wordings, which
I have attached in the description of this video.
In this short, you or your nominee can
take maturity yearly, half-yearly, quarterly, or monthly. You can
also pay top-up premiums to the company from time to time.
Another special feature of this policy is that
you can withdraw
20% of the fund value
once every year after five years of purchasing the policy. This means
you can withdraw 20% of the fund value once a year,
or you
can withdraw 6% of the fund value every year under the systematic withdrawal plan after five years of purchasing the policy.
This policy is available for ₹50 lakh or ₹1 crore.
You can pay regular premiums in this policy from the beginning or in 12 years.
This policy is
available for 30 or 40 years.  This policy can be
taken by people between 18 years to 60 years
and the maximum maturity in this policy is
85 years. Thank you for watching this video. I
hope you have understood this plan well
and if I have
explained it to you with full hard work then
like this video, comment, share
and subscribe to my channel. Thanks
again.